Long long ago
Through the winter-worn land
There wandered
A hungry girl alone
In the words of a distant foreign land
You offered the same prayer
again and again
Long long ago
Through the winter-worn land
O King ah my King
A warm
embrace
I am
the blue unraveling
The offered
angel of innocence
O King ah my King
Bestow upon us
Your great guidance
I am
the blue soul
The faithful
angel of prayer
O King ah my King
Bestow upon us
pure joy
I am
the blue destiny
The faithful
angel of yours
Once more
Bestow upon us
your mercy
By your breath
We shall be saved
We seek
awakening to love
O king ah my King
Bestow upon us
A warm embrace
I am
the blue unraveling
SEVEN YEARS AGO
IN FRONT OF THE ALTAR
INSIDE NERGAL
Long long ago
Through the winter-worn land
There wandered
A hungry girl alone
The villagers
Living in poverty
Shared with her
A single piece of their meager bread
While you waited for spring to come
In return for the warmth you were given
In the words of a distant foreign land
You offered the same prayer
PRINCESS KNIGHT
TEZUKA OSAMU